Inventory of the Francis E. Warren Papers, 1867-1974
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series I. Political Papers, 1878-1945
  - Subseries 2. General Business Correspondence, 1878-1932; 5 cubic ft. (28 books)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 3, 1880-Jan. 4, 1881; microfilm reel 108 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 4, 1881-Dec. 31, 1881; microfilm reel 109 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, July 14, 1881-May 18, 1883; microfilm reel 110 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, June 3, 1882-Jan. 1, 1883; microfilm reel 111 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, May 19, 1883-Feb. 24, 1884; microfilm reel 112 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, July 6, 1885-Jan. 29, 1887; microfilm reel 113 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 7, 1890-Nov. 15, 1894; microfilm reel 114 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, June 30, 1892-June 30, 1893; microfilm reel 115 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 16, 1892-Jan. 31, 1894; microfilm reel 116 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 10, 1894-Aug. 7, 1896; microfilm reel 116 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 10, 1898-Jan. 31, 1901; microfilm reel 117 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 2, 1901-Dec. 31, 1903; microfilm reel 118 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 23, 1898-Dec. 7, 1903; microfilm reel 118 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 1, 1904-Dec. 31, 1905; microfilm reel 119 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 1, 1906-June 11, 1908; microfilm reel 120 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, June 11, 1908-June 17, 1910; microfilm reel 121 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, June 18, 1910-Feb. 14, 1912; microfilm reel 122 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 14, 1912-Dec. 20, 1913; microfilm reel 123 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 22, 1913-July 13, 1915; microfilm reel 124 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, July 14, 1915-Nov. 5, 1917; microfilm reel 125 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 6, 1917-Sept. 25, 1919; microfilm reel 126 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 27, 1919-May 5, 1921; microfilm reel 127 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, May 5, 1921-Sept. 15, 1923; microfilm reel 128 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 11, 1923-June 5, 1925; microfilm reel 129 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, June 6, 1925-Aug. 8, 1928; microfilm reel 130 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, microfilm reel 131; Dec. 26, 1928-May 29, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 11, 1928-Sept. 3, 1932; microfilm reel 132 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3. F. E. Warren General Correspondence, 1888-1896; 1.5 cubic ft. (10 books)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 23, 1888-Dec. 31, 1888; microfilm reel 133 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 31, 1888-May 22, 1889; microfilm reel 134 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 21, 1889-Feb. 5, 1890; microfilm reel 134 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 6, 1890-Sept. 22, 1890; microfilm reel 135 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 22, 1890-June 5, 1891; microfilm reel 135 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 3, 1891-Dec. 8, 1891; microfilm reel 136 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 9, 1891-June 29, 1892; microfilm reel 136 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 31, 1894-Nov. 13, 1894; microfilm reel 137 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 14, 1894-May 9, 1895; microfilm reel 137 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - F. E. Warren, General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 8, 1895-Sept. 2, 1896; microfilm reel 138 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - F. E. Warren Private and Political Correspondence, 1896-1898; Subseries 4.; .5 cubic ft. (4 books)
    Arranged chronologically. Letterpress copybooks including political and personal correspondence.
    - F. E. Warren, Private and Political Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 8, 1896-Sept. 17, 1896; microfilm reel 139 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - F. E. Warren, Private and Political Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 17, 1896-Oct. 7, 1896; microfilm reel 139 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - F. E. Warren, Private and Political Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 7,1896-Oct. 25, 1896; microfilm reel 140 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - F. E. Warren, Private and Political Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 24, 1896-Oct. 15, 1898; microfilm reel 140 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5. Governor Warren Papers, 1885-1892; .75 cubic feet (4 books and 1 document box)
    Arranged chronologically and alphabetically. Letterpress copybooks, correspondence, documents and other records created during Warren's tenure as governor. Also includes some correspondence of Governor Amos W. Barber.
    - Governor of Wyoming Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 1, 1885-Aug. 15, 1892; microfilm reel 141 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Governor of Wyoming Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 9, 1889-Nov. 11, 1889; microfilm reel 141 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Governor of Wyoming Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 11, 1889-May 17, 1890; microfilm reel 142 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Governor of Wyoming Correspondence: Letterbook, May 17, 1890-Nov. 26, 1890; microfilm reel 142 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Rock Springs Riot of 1885, 1885-1886; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-June 1885; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, July-Dec. 1885; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1886; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Apr.-June 1886; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, July-Dec. 1886; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1888; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1889; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1890; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1891; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1892; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Telegrams, 1884-1886,n.d.; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Documents of Elections, 1873-1890; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Telegrams, 1880-1895; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Official Notifications and Requests, 1881-1890; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Personal Expenses, Accounts, 1886-1890; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Report of the Governor of Wyoming to the Secretary of the Interior, 1889; microfilm reel 143 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 6. Senator Warren Papers, 1890-1945; 1.2 cubic ft. (3 document boxes)
    Correspondence and letterpress copybooks regarding Warren's senate years.
    - Autographs of Congressmen, President, Vice President, 1893,1907,1909; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Autograph Letters from Presidents, 1897-1929; (Originals in safe); microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Amendments before Congress, 1891-1919; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Calendar of Business, 60th Congress, 1908; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Advertisements, Speech by F. W. Mondell, 1896,1910; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Certificates of Election, 1895-1919; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1892; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1892-1929; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence about Vote on Location of Capital, 1904; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Invitation and Program for 1917 Presidential Inauguration, microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Personal Expenses, Accounts, 1890-1920; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Speech of F.E.W.-"The League of Nations", 1919; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Wyoming Primary and General Election Returns, 1914,1916; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Published and Legal Documents, 1909-1923; Act of Tariff, speeches delivered by F. E. Warren, letter (copy) from Theodore Roosevelt; microfilm reel 144 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - President's Message on Wool Industry, Vol. I, II, 1912; microfilm reel 145 (Box 32A, Folder 1)
    - President's Message on Wool Industry, vol. III, IV, 1912; microfilm reel 145 (Box 32A, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Report of the Joint Commission of Agricultural Inquiry, 67th U.S. Congress, 1921; microfilm reel 145 (Box 32A, Folder 3)
    - The Protectionist, Sept. 1916, Nov. 1917; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32A, Folder 4)
    - Wool Industry Hearings Before U.S. Senate, 1938,1945; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32A, Folder 5)
    - School Budgets for Western Schools, 1889-1896; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32A, Folder 6)
    - Senate Document #458, Wool and Manufactures of Wool, Presented by Senator Warren, Mar. 25, 1910; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32A, Folder 7)
    - United States Senate Committee of Appropriations: Letterbook, Apr. 24, 1911-Mar. 8, 1913; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32B, Folder 1)
    - F. E. Warren's Voting Record in Congress, 1913-1918; microfilm reel 146 (Box 32B, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 7. Military Papers, 1898-1912; 1.5 cubic ft. (1 document box, 2 slim document boxes, and 2 books)
    Letterpress copybooks and correspondence. Includes information on Senator Warren's military pension.
    - Index of Checks for Back Pay of Wyoming Volunteers, 1900-1910; microfilm reel 147 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Investigation of Expenditures in War Department, U.S. Congress, 1911,1912; microfilm reel 147 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Medals of Honor Circular, 1904-1909; microfilm reel 147 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Soldiers' Homestead Claims, 1907; microfilm reel 147 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - F. E. Warren Scrapbook, Personal Interest Wyoming Volunteers, 1898-1901; microfilm reel 147 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - U. S. Senate Committee on Military Affairs: Letterbook, Jan. 11, 1906-July 5, 1909; microfilm reel 147 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Military Affairs, July 14, 1909-Apr. 25, 1911; microfilm reel 147 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Pensions, Apr. 23, 1897-Jan. 30, 1900; microfilm reel 148 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Pension Letters, Jan. 26, 1900-Oct. 29, 1904; microfilm reel 148 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Pension Letters, Nov. 1, 1904-Mar. 16, 1909; microfilm reel 149 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Pensions Letters, Mar. 17, 1909-Mar. 25, 1913; microfilm reel 149 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Pensions, Apr. 16, 1913-Aug. 28, 1917; microfilm reel 150 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Pensions, Aug. 22, 1917-Oct. 19, 1918; microfilm reel 150 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 8. Scrapbooks, 1880-1929; 10 cubic ft. (29 books)
    Scrapbooks of political and business subjects and travels. Includes clippings, photographs and documents.
    - Scrapbook: Business, 1909-1914,n.d.; microfilm reel 151 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Trip, 1903-1905; Teddy Roosevelt's visit to Wyoming 1903; Frontier Days 1903; Roosevelt Administration Inauguration 1905; microfilm reel 151 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Trip, 1907; Trip to Europe 1907; microfilm reel 151 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Trip, 1915; Trip to Hawaii; San Francisco Exposition; Legislators study conditions in Hawaii; microfilm reel 151 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook: Trip, 1905; Guest of Secretary Taft; Philippines 1905; Visit to Manila; microfilm reel 152 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Trip, 1915; Taft party in Philippine Islands, Manila, China 1915; Alice Roosevelt; microfilm reel 152 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1900-1906; Personal 1900-1906; Stands on miscellaneous bills; Warren family; Wyoming politics and history; Death of Mrs. Warren; wool; Pershing marriage; Warren accused of fraud; microfilm reel 152 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1900-1904; Scrapbook: Political Politics and history 1900-1904; Outstanding events in the state: Death of Chief Washakie 1900, T. R. Roosevelt visits Cheyenne 190(?), Death of Esther Morris 1902, Fifth Annual Frontier Days 1901, Casper jail-break and Woodward lynching 1902, Cheyenne Opera house burns 1902, DeForest Richards Scandal, Death of Gov. Richards 1903, Forts McKenzie and Russell improvements; Convention and election of 1900; Convention and election of 1902; Convention and election of 1904; Assassination of Pres. McKinley; R. W. Breckons-Appointment to U.S. Attorney, Hawaii; Van DeVanter appointment to district judge 1903; Monitor "Wyoming"; microfilm reel 153 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1904-1911; Political and history 1904-1911; Chattert and Warren feud 1905; Investigation of Warren for fraud 1905; Shoshone Reservation and irrigation; Wool growers and sheep industry; Wool Tariff 1909; Wyoming's Resources; Enlargement of Fort Russell; Warren's visit to Philippines and Japan 1905; Election of 1906, 1908, 1910; Frontier Days Celebrations 1906, 1907, 1908, 1910, good pictures and history; Taft visits Cheyenne; Roosevelt visits Cheyenne 1910; Battleship "Wyoming"; Carey-Warren split 1910; Van DeVanter named associate justice 1910; Building of Plains Hotel; Warren Chairman of Senate Appropriation Committee 1910; microfilm reel 154 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1906-1910; microfilm reel 155 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1911-1912; Campaign of 1912; microfilm reel 156 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1912-1913; Campaign of 1912; microfilm reel 156 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1912-1918; Campaign of 1912, 1914, 1916, 1918; microfilm reel 157 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1918-1928; Political and historical; World War I events; Death of Willis George Emerson; Death of Angus Charles Baker; Mondell-floor leader of House; History of Woman Suffrage; Storm 1920; Election and campaign of 1924; Chief Washakie; Deming named to Civil Service; Frances Pershing Memorial; microfilm reel 157 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Political, Aug. 1911-Nov. 1918; Political and historical, campaign clippings 1918; microfilm reel 158 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, Dec. 1910-May 1914; Personal 1910-1914; Warren Chairman of Senate Appropriation Committee 1911; Plains Hotel; Marriage of Clara Morgan 1911; miscellaneous criticisms; Pershing in Philippines; 1913 Tariff and wool; microfilm reel 158 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1924-1929; Personal 1924-1929; Campaign of 1924; The Warren myth growing; The Pershing family; Mount Warren, Wyoming; Death of Warren; microfilm reel 159 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1928-1929; Politics and history 1928-1929; Election of 1928; Burlington Depot for Cheyenne; Hoover visits Cheyenne; Frontier Days 1928; Johnson County War and early history; Teton National Park; Washakie and Grace R. Hebard; Death of Warren and his successor; microfilm reel 159 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1914-1918; Personal 1914-1918; The Washington scene; Woman suffrage; Death of Mrs. Pershing; Miscellaneous national events; Pershing in Mexico; Intention to retire in 1919; Pershing and World War I; Warren enters 1918 campaign; microfilm reel 160 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1918-1924; Personal 1918-1924; World War I; Pershing; National events and politics; Wyoming-irrigation; microfilm reel 160 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Political, Feb. 14, 1880-Mar. 28, 1889; microfilm reel 160 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, Jan. 1, 1892-Jan. 1, 1900; Senatorial career and Letter Book Dec. 1894-Mar. 1895; microfilm reel 161 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1893-1896; Politics 1893-1896; Laramie County affairs and politics; Elections of 1894 and 1896; Benjamin Harrison visits Cheyenne; Gov. Richards; microfilm reel 162 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1897-1899; Politics 1897-1899; Cheyenne City politics; Laramie County politics; Elections 1898-1899; Miscellaneous Senatorial activities; Frontier Days-August 1899; microfilm reel 162 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1889-1891; microfilm reel 162 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1890-1893; Wyoming statehood; Campaign and election; Election of 1892; Johnson County War; State politics; microfilm reel 163 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1910; microfilm reel 163 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1910; microfilm reel 163 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Political, 1924-1926; Warren and Wyoming politics; Miscellaneous National political events 1924-1926; microfilm reel 163 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Series II. Personal Papers, 1868-1974
  - Francis E. Warren Correspondence, 1868-1929; Subseries 1.; 5.28 cubic ft. (11 document boxes)
    Correspondence deals with all aspects of Francis E. Warrens life: personal, business, sheep raising, wool and politics. This series is divided into 2 subseries:
    - Subsubseries 1. Francis E. Warren Correspondence with Fred E. Warren, 1912-1929
      - December 30, 1912-March 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - April 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - May-June 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - July 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - August 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - September, December 1913, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - January-February 1914, microfilm reel 164 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - March 1914, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - April 1914, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - May 1914, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - June-December 1914, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - January-April 16, 1915, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - April-December 1915, microfilm reel 164 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - January 1905, March 1907, microfilm reel 164 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - January-February 1916, microfilm reel 164 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - March 1916, microfilm reel 164 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - April-May 1916, microfilm reel 165 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - June-August 12, 1916, microfilm reel 165 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - August 16-December 1916, microfilm reel 165 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - January-February 1917, microfilm reel 165 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - March-April 1917, microfilm reel 165 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - May 1917, microfilm reel 165 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - June-December 1917, microfilm reel 165 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - January-February 1918, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - March-April 1918, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - May, July 1918, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - August-October 11, 1918, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - October 23-December 1918, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - January-June 1919, microfilm reel 165 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - July-October 1919, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - November 1919-February 1920, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - March-December 1920, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - January-March 1921, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - April-June 1921, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - July-December 1921, microfilm reel 166 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - January-March 1922, microfilm reel 166 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - April-July 1922, microfilm reel 166 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - August 1922-January 1923, microfilm reel 166 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - February-December 1923, microfilm reel 166 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - January-May 1924, microfilm reel 167 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - June 1924-February 1925, microfilm reel 167 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - March-December 1925, microfilm reel 167 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - January-March 1926, microfilm reel 167 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - April-May 1926, microfilm reel 167 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - June-December 1926, microfilm reel 167 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - January-May 1927, microfilm reel 167 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - June-November 1927, microfilm reel 167 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - December 1927-February 22, 1928, microfilm reel 167 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - February 23-April 1928, microfilm reel 168 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - May-October 1928, microfilm reel 168 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - November-December 1928, microfilm reel 168 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - January-March 1929, microfilm reel 168 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - April-May 1929, microfilm reel 168 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - June-October 17, 1929, microfilm reel 168 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - October 19-November 1929, microfilm reel 168 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous no Dates, n.d.; microfilm reel 168 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Subsubseries 2. Correspondence with Helen Smith, 1868-1902
      - March 1868-March 1869, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - February 1869-March 1869, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - April 1869-December 1869, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - April 1870-June 1870, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - June 1870-August 1870, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - August 1870-October 1870, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - October 1870-December 1870, microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Helen Smith Correspondence, 1899-1902; microfilm reel 169 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2. Fred E. Warren Correspondence, 1903-1949; 2.25 cubic ft. (3 document boxes, 6 letterbooks).
    The letterbooks are arranged chronologically, boxes are arranged alphabetically. Correspondence deals with personal, business and associational matters. This series is divided into 3 subseries:
    - Subsubseries 1. General Outgoing Correspondence, 1903-1949
      - Letterbook, 1903-1913; microfilm reel 170 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Letterbook, 1913-1921; microfilm reel 171 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Letterbook, 1921-1929; microfilm reel 172 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Letterbook, 1929-1935; microfilm reel 173 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Letterbook, 1935-1942; microfilm reel 174 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Letterbook, 1942-1949; microfilm reel 175 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Subsubseries 2. General Correspondence, 1913-1946
      - A, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - B, 1914-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - C, 1915-1931; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - D, 1909-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - E, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - F, 1927-1931; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - G, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - H, 1903-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Harvard, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - I, J, 1912-1923; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - K, L, 1912-1931; microfilm reel 176 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - M, N, 1913-1930; microfilm reel 176 (Box 59, Folder 1)